mrisoftware.com 2015-06-22

# MRI Software Privacy Policy

#####  MRI Software LLC Website Privacy Policy

MRI Software LLC (“MRI,” the “Company,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) will endeavor to protect and develop or use technology that provides a safer online experience for the customer/consumer (“you” or “your”) and has created this privacy statement (the “Privacy Policy”) to demonstrate its firm commitment to secure and trustworthy Internet commerce and the individual's privacy.  
BY USING THIS WEB SITE AND ANY WEB PAGES AND CONTENT THEREIN (COLLECTIVELY, THE “SITE”), YOU CONSENT TO THE TERMS OF MRI’S PRIVACY POLICY AND TO MRI'S PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR THE PURPOSES SET FORTH BELOW.

#####  Registration

You may be required to register in order to be granted access to certain information, services and/or products at this Site. At the time of registration, you may be prompted by one of our online forms to provide certain personal information to us, including your name, company name, and email address.

#####  Use of Your Personal Information

The personal information that you provide to MRI, may be stored, processed, and used by MRI and its affiliates for the following purposes: (a) to provide information about our company, products and/or services, including updates, notifications, and details of any offers or promotions; (b) to assist us in improving our products, services or the content of this Site; (c) to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop better products; (d) for our own internal marketing and research purposes; (e) to promote user groups; (f) to make this Site or service easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing this Site or service to your particular interests or preferences; (g) to analyze information for trends and statistics. We may also provide this information to an agent acting on MRI's behalf in connection with the activities described above.

MRI will occasionally hire other companies, which use cookies, to provide limited services on our behalf, such as packaging, sending, and delivering purchases and other mailings; answering customer questions about products or services; processing event registration; or performing statistical analysis of our services. MRI will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service and any such personal information shall be subject to the third party companies’ privacy policies.

You also hereby grant to MRI a perpetual, non-cancelable, worldwide, non-exclusive right to utilize any data that arises from the use of this Site or any MRI or its affiliates’ products by you for any legitimate business purpose, including the right to sublicense such data to third parties, subject to all legal restrictions regarding the use and disclosure of such information.

Except as described above, MRI will not sell, rent, or in any way intentionally disclose personal information that you provide to us on this Site to any third party (other than an agent acting on our behalf as described above), unless: (a) MRI is required to do so by law, regulation, warrant, subpoena or court order, (b) MRI is required in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of MRI employees, users of MRI products or services, or members of the public, or to enforce provisions of the Terms of Use; or (c) such disclosure is part of a sale or transfer of all (or substantially all) of the assets or stock of MRI or one or more divisions or affiliates of MRI .

#####  Use of Cookies

MRI uses cookies to help us provide better customer service and to enhance the user experience and deliver personalized content. Many improvements and updates to this Site are based on the data collected through the cookies, such as total number of visitors and pages viewed. A "cookie" is a small text file stored locally in the computer used to access your account, and contains information relating to your past use of this Site. MRI may disclose the non-personally identifiable information collected, in aggregate form only, to third parties including advertisers or potential advertisers. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive feature of this Site or services you visit.

#####  Bulletin Boards and Chat Rooms

From time to time, portions of this Site may allow you to post information which other visitors to this Site will be able to access (such as on a "bulletin board" or during an interactive "chat" with other visitors). In the event that you choose to post information in this context, it becomes generally available to the public, and we have no ability to control or limit its use by visitors to our site. By posting the information on this Site you are providing MRI and its affiliates the right to use the information in connection with the operation of MRI's business. Therefore, we encourage you not to post any information you consider private or sensitive on this Site.

#####  Children's Privacy

MRI's Site, software and services do not target, and are not structured to attract, children under the age of 13. MRI does not collect any registration information from users who indicate they are under the age of 13. If MRI discovers personal data from a child, MRI will eliminate that data.

#####  Safe Harbor Privacy Policy

MRI adheres to the Safe Harbor Agreement between the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission with respect to personally identifiable information that is transferred from the European Economic Area to the United States within the scope of MRI’s Safe Harbor certification. Read more about our **Safe Harbor** policy.

#####  Security of Information

To protect the privacy of personal information provided by you, MRI employs industry-standard controls including physical access controls, Internet firewalls, intrusion detection, and network monitoring. Additionally, only authorized administrators and staff have access to systems containing such information. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.

#####  Revisions

MRI reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you, and MRI will post any changes to this Privacy Policy on this Site as soon as they go into effect. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

Effective Date:  June 1, 2014
